<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>Overseer releases</title>
		<link>https://www.gamesystems.com/software/joverseer/betafeed.xml</link>
		<description>The latest version of jOverseer, the Middle-Earth game
			helper program.</description>
		<language>en</language>
				<item>
			<title>1.18.19-rc4</title>
			<pubDate>19 February 2025</pubDate>
			<description>
VERSION 1.18.19-rc4
---------------
- Improvements and bug fixes to Nation Colours 
	- Auto sets preference to use custo colours on editing colours
	- New folder location in AppData
	- Saves which colour file to use for a game file
	- Can edit file names 
- HomePage Image width 0 bug fix
			</description>
			</item>	
		<item>
			<title>1.18.19-rc3</title>
			<pubDate>7 February 2025</pubDate>
			<description>
VERSION 1.18.19-rc3
---------------
- Edit Nations Colour in Edit Nation Details!
- The option to use custom colours is in preferences, Map, and Nation Colours
- In the Edit Nation Details form, you can create different Colour Sets, the one you use is the one selected in the drop down (becomes the default for the current game)
			</description>
			</item>	
		<item>
			<title>1.18.19-rc2</title>
			<pubDate>31 January 2025</pubDate>
			<description>
VERSION 1.18.19-rc2
---------------
- Orderchecker bug fix for results disapearing/not clearing themselves
- Fixed Order table autocompletion box being weird with typing (hopefully)
			</description>
			</item>	
						<item>
			<title>1.18.19-rc1</title>
			<pubDate>30 January 2025</pubDate>
			<description>
VERSION 1.18.19-rc1
---------------
- Orderchecker now saves results for each nation orderchecked, for each turn, and stores them in jov file
- Orderchecker now has a Tick box for saying if you are ok with errors and warnings
- Submit Orders now doesnt have lots of pop-ups. Just green/yellow/red icon by nation name indicating orderchecker result
- Orderchecker now has name of nation
			</description>
			</item>	
				<item>
			<title>1.18.18-rc1</title>
			<pubDate>27 January 2025</pubDate>
			<description>
VERSION 1.18.18-rc1
---------------
- Fixes for Other Locales
			</description>
			</item>	
		<item>
			<title>1.18.17-rc13</title>
			<pubDate>21 January 2025</pubDate>
			<description>
VERSION 1.18.17-rc13
---------------
- Fixes
			</description>
			</item>	
				<item>
			<title>1.18.17-rc12</title>
			<pubDate>14 January 2025</pubDate>
			<description>
VERSION 1.18.17-rc12
---------------
- Small bug fixes
			</description>
			</item>	
		<item>
			<title>1.18.17-rc11</title>
			<pubDate>8 January 2025</pubDate>
			<description>
VERSION 1.18.17-rc11
---------------
- Force Compatibility Stuff (Set order preference + show Notepad)
- Home View changes to orders due etc
- Tidy code and warnings up
- Remove 'Show log' button
- Fix bug - 'PC attack info'
			</description>
			</item>	
			<item>
			<title>1.18.17-rc10</title>
			<pubDate>16 December 2024</pubDate>
			<description>
VERSION 1.18.17-rc10
---------------
- 'Strength of Attacking armies' Column now added to armies
- Strength changed to 'base Strength', showing strength before any modifiers which change between armies and PC are applied
- New 'Combat Log' button, shows numbers and calculations 
			</description>
			</item>	
			<item>
			<title>1.18.17-rc9</title>
			<pubDate>4 December 2024</pubDate>
			<description>
VERSION 1.18.17-rc9
---------------
- Fixed TurnReportView double agent bug
- Introduced .csv for climate and terrain modifiers for 'Regions' (1000 games)
- Drop down menu for each army to select what region it is
- If an army doesnt have completed info (eg has command rank or morale set to 0) then will make it yellow 
			</description>
			</item>	
						<item>
			<title>1.18.17-rc8</title>
			<pubDate>25 November 2024</pubDate>
			<description>
VERSION 1.18.17-rc8
---------------
- Recent Games (changes to internal storing and getting)
- Recent games now say whether you have 1. Not submitted orders for this turn 2. If you need to import new results (current date is after dur date) 3. when you last submitted orders
- Orderchecker fixes, MovComp wasn't waiting for state updates to do with joining/creating companies
- Orderchecker Error checking if camp is there (neutral camp)
- ExportOrders now closes on release
- Combat calc - relations for pop center can now be edited (and imported properly)
- Armies automatically get defense points added from fortification bonus
			</description>
			</item>	
				<item>
			<title>1.18.17-rc7</title>
			<pubDate>14 November 2024</pubDate>
			<description>
VERSION 1.18.17-rc7
---------------
- Fixed War machines
    - Now count towards army combats (50)
    - Were counting doubly for fortifications
- Adjusted Size of panel and components
- Fixed bug with removing armies from first table
- 'Add army' now automatically opens edit menu
- Fix - Hex numbers which begin with a '0' wasnt importing armies properly, fixed now
- New 'before/after' option, showing troop numbers before and after combat
			</description>
			</item>	
		<item>
			<title>1.18.17-rc6</title>
			<pubDate>11 November 2024</pubDate>
			<description>
VERSION 1.18.17-rc6
---------------
- Rounding error when calculating combat modifier
			</description>
			</item>	
				<item>
			<title>1.18.17-rc5</title>
			<pubDate>8 November 2024</pubDate>
			<description>
VERSION 1.18.17-rc5
---------------
- updated troopvstactic, tacticvstactic and troopterrain tables for correct values
			</description>
			</item>	
		<item>
			<title>1.18.17-rc4</title>
			<pubDate>7 November 2024</pubDate>
			<description>
VERSION 1.18.17-rc4
---------------
- Can see tactic in combat form
- Hopefully fixed Home, Recent games from going to a second line
			</description>
			</item>	
				<item>
			<title>1.18.17-rc3</title>
			<pubDate>4 November 2024</pubDate>
			<description>
VERSION 1.18.17-rc3
---------------
- '+' tab in notepad to add new notes
- descriptive text in notepad to guide user how to use
- Home page recent games: Icon showing whether or not orders have been sent this turn, upon mouseover tooltip says when you submitted them.
- Send orders pane now closes after submit
- reversed recent games list
- Copy and save orders now copy/save all selected nations orders
- Legal copyright stuff put in home page
- Fixed notepad layout issue
- Fixed other text issues
			</description>
			</item>	
		<item>
			<title>1.18.17-rc2</title>
			<pubDate>28 October 2024</pubDate>
			<description>
VERSION 1.18.17-rc2
---------------
- New notepad tab
   - In Tools -> General -> Notepad
   - Right click on tabs to edit, new note or delete
   - Constant between turns
- Submit orders, further redesign
- Orderchecker fixes
   - 820 order even if failed (not commander) updated char position
   - DsbComp didnt properly remove them from company
- Homeview now has default view with no internet
- Fix Preference not hiding/showing edit order button
			</description>
			</item>	
		<item>
			<title>1.18.17-rc1</title>
			<pubDate>21 October 2024</pubDate>
			<description>
VERSION 1.18.17-rc1
---------------
	* Combat calculator changes:
		* Auto loads relations for each army
		* Add new table, all other armies in hex go here, including neutral armies, can drag and drop them across
		* Now a "refresh combat button" in case things go wrong...
	* No longer warns players about neutral armies or popcenters
	* Moved things around in send orders pane to try and make things clearer
	* New preference tab, for default pages
	* Preference for disabling orders on characters you dont control
			</description>
			</item>	
		<item>
			<title>1.18.16-rc1</title>
			<pubDate>21 October 2024</pubDate>
			<description>
VERSION 1.18.16-rc1
---------------
	*ArmyViewer bug fix, crashing on enemy navy but no 'elements'
			</description>
			</item>	
		<item>
			<title>1.18.15-rc5</title>
			<pubDate>30 September 2024</pubDate>
			<description>
VERSION 1.18.15-rc5
---------------
	*Small Bug fixes
	*Loading a game opens map view
	*Importing order results go to turn report
			</description>
			</item>	
			<item>
			<title>1.18.15-rc4</title>
			<pubDate>9 September 2024</pubDate>
			<description>
VERSION 1.18.15-rc4
---------------
	*Fixes for orderchecker
	*Arti changes
	*Edit nation Data form fix
			</description>
			</item>	
			<item>
			<title>1.18.15-rc3</title>
			<pubDate>6 September 2024</pubDate>
			<description>
VERSION 1.18.15-rc3
---------------
	* Fixes for Home Page
		- Formatting and functionality issues
		- Preference for it to be landing page
	* Orderchecker fixes
		- Company logic fully working
		- Neutral nations working with 'isEnemy' using relations
		- 550 555 orders work now
	* Other
		- Submit orders fixes
		- Double Agents being overwritten by other nations files fixed
		- Reverse sort recent games
			</description>
			</item>	
			<item>
			<title>1.18.15-rc2</title>
			<pubDate>6 August 2024</pubDate>
			<description>
VERSION 1.18.15-rc2
---------------
	* New Home Page
		- Main view is weekly newsletter
		- Side panel has recent games or info on how to start new game
	* Submit multiple orders for multiple nations
	* Fixed few beta bugs
		- Orderchecker fixes 
		- Reverse sort recent games
			</description>
		</item>		
			<item>
			<title>1.18.15-rc1</title>
			<pubDate>2 July 2024</pubDate>
			<description>
VERSION 1.18.15-rc1
---------------
	* Enh: Orderchecker more accurately includes and uses Companies when checking orders
	* Enh: Recent Games Menu now sorts by orders due 
	* Enh: Added preference (automatically on) to automatically clear old/innactive games from Recent Games Menu
	* recent games menu now refreshes upon saving game
	* Fixed orders not loading for sone characters after importing xml
	* 940 412 now showing 6 artis
	* Nation selection no longer greys out blue arrow, now disables edit order buttons
	* Fixed comparator, character order in hex view should now ignore accents

			</description>
		</item>		
			<item>
			<title>1.18.14-rc3</title>
			<pubDate>7 Jun 2024</pubDate>
			<description>
	VERSION 1.18.14-rc3
    ---------------
	* Enh: Artifact Table now editable.
	* QA: Armies in Current Hex View reformatted to be clearer.
	* QA: Turn Report View has highlights section at top.
	* Fix: Diplo turn number out by one, now corrected.

			</description>
		</item>		
		<item>
			<title>1.18.14-rc2</title>
			<pubDate>17 May 2024</pubDate>
			<description>
VERSION 1.18.14-rc2
-------------------
	* Enh: artifact table is now editable
			</description>
		</item>	
		<item>
			<title>1.18.14-rc1</title>
			<pubDate>8 May 2024</pubDate>
			<description>
VERSION 1.18.14-rc1
-------------------
	* Fix: Added secondary artifact powers for new KS games.
	* Fix: Added scrolling to Diplo panel.
	* Enh: Moved some of the map options to map preferences.
	* Enh: Reformatted Army part of Current Hex View.
			</description>
		</item>	
		<item>
			<title>1.18.12-rc3</title>
			<pubDate>20 Mar 2024</pubDate>
			<description>
	VERSION 1.18.12-rc3
    ---------------
	* Enh: When importing a turn file, ONLY filenames of the current game are listed.
	* Enh: Lots of small tweaks to diplomatic message support.
	* Enh: New Map Option to visibly mark the Capitals of Nations on the Map.
	* Enh: On the Economy Calculator, marking a pop. center as lost will select that hex on the map.
	* Enh: Change Dragons section of InfoView to link to the more up-to-date wiki. Offer to open in default browser.
	* Enh: In the Current Hex View, don't show orders for dead characters.
	* Enh: Export Orders now lets you submit 'shadow' orders.
	* Enh: A clearer method of selecting nations on the Diplo Form.
	* Enh: A marker appears on the title bar to warn you when looking at old turns.	 
	* QA: Restrict file types when exporting orders and diplos, to avoid user error accidentally trashing files.
	* QA: Check For Update is more in-your-face when mentioning that no update is needed.
	* Fix: Repeated imports of turn 0 were failing to update starting character stats.
	* Fix: Failing a RA cast no longer creates a spurious artifact.
	* Fix: Empty Notes are removed. The red exclamation mark is gone.
	* Fix: Showing navy range now toggles on/off properly on the map.
	* Fix: Showing navy range now works on open seas.
	* Fix: Some cases where importing orders, broke intelligence of nation's capital location.
	* Fix: Battle reports of destroyed PCs are no longer ignored.
	* Fix: The population attack statistics for expected losses and remainder was swapped.

			</description>
		</item>		
		<item>
			<title>1.18.11</title>
			<pubDate>28 Feb 2024</pubDate>
			<description>
		VERSION 1.18.11-rc2
		---------------
		* Fix: if a submission to meturn fails, then tell the player.
		* Enh: Send Diplomatic messages with orders. See the File menu.
		* Enh: Send Diplomatic messages to multiple nations.
		* Enh: Past diplomatic messages are stored with the turn, and accessible in their own View.
		* Enh: Tell player if a Diplo is due this turn (from XML information).
		* QA: Support turn PDF changes to GSI rebranding.
		* Fix: (incomplete) Some order text imports breaking with default names and genders.
			</description>
		</item>		
		<item>
			<title>1.18.10</title>
			<pubDate>14 Feb 2024</pubDate>
			<description>
			VERSION 1.18.10
			---------------
			* Enh: Add power2 for discovered artifacts
			* Enh: Support for overriding default allegiances and removing nations after importing.
			* QA: gamesystems.com updates
			* QA: enhancing update process.
			* Enh: Updates to combat calc for new rules.
			* Fix: oddities with some artifact names fixed. (crown of Celethsa, Morgul Knives)
			</description>
		</item>		
		<item>
			<title>1.18.9</title>
			<pubDate>5 Oct 2023</pubDate>
			<description>
			VERSION 1.18.9
			--------------
			* Fix: Casting Locate Artifact on an owned artifact wasn't being noticed.
			* Fix: Female spell-casters had palantir results ignored.
			* Fix: combat overwriting camped ruins
			* Fix: Scout Pop Center now checks that its information is better than the existing information about the popcenter.
			* Fix: 1650 characters Herumor and Jirfelien stats updated.
			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>1.18.8</title>
			<pubDate>20 July 2023</pubDate>
			<description>
			VERSION 1.18.8
			--------------
			* Fix: correcting the typo of the Kidnap SNAs 31,45 broke old games where they were used.
			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>1.18.7</title>
			<pubDate>20 July 2023</pubDate>
			<description>
				VERSION 1.18.7
				--------------
				* Enh: support Bring-Your-Own Java
				* Fix: Some artifacts were not reconciled by name.
				* Fix: Quick order Recon 930 actually added a 925 order.
				* Fix: Duplicated artifact in RA broke import
				* Fix: Fix a couple of cases where docks would not appear on reports
				* Fix: Scrying with an artifact 
					+ caused JO to interpret the Recon result as if the artifact was the name of the army commander.
				* Fix: {0} appearing in messages.
				* Fix: Wrong artifact shown in character view.
				* Fix: Army fed calculations on NPC PopC broke current hex view. 
			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>1.18.6</title>
			<pubDate>13 June 2023</pubDate>
			<description>
				VERSION 1.18.6
				--------------
				fix: NPCs recruited now showing on nation statistics
				fix: certain case of army not being fed from PC
				fix: a case where PC details not being updating based on army presence.
				fix: Ruins not appearing after battle.
				fix: Updated character limits for CMF
			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>1.18.5</title>
			<pubDate>30 May 2023</pubDate>
			<description>
				VERSION 1.18.5
				--------------
	* Enh: Support for new SNA buy/sell at 10%
	* Fix: When feeding Armies, Ruins of 'no' nation broke the Current Hex View.
			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>1.18.4</title>
			<pubDate>26 May 2023</pubDate>
			<description>
				VERSION 1.18.4
				--------------
	* Enh: Armies now appear to feed themselves from PCs in some cases.
	* Enh: Combat imports armies and PC. Added to hex pop-up menu.
		+ Thanks Jon!
	* Enh: Combat calc, add PC, estimate armies from recons.
	* Enh: Apply army size processing fix to all games, not just KS
	* Enh: default map zoom factor is saved as a preference.
	* Enh: Support randomized artifacts in 1650 games
		+ JO will re-write the known artifact ids to 0 when the first XML is imported.
	* Fix: Order-checking status should stay more in sync with the rest of JO.
	* Fix: Reveal Character True results now get recognised again in character reports.    
	* Fix: Orderchecker now notices two 810 orders.
	* Fix: Broken pdf parsing due to license name changes.
	* Fix: Marked JO as not dpiAware, and added some rendering hints to try and improve map hex readability.
	 (there are still problems with certain combinations)
	* Fix: Army maintenance calculation display in Army View.
	* Fix: Army composition display in Army View.
	* Fix: Captured/Lost PCs now recorded under new owner from battle report.
	* Fix: PC Size and Fort are now correct when reported in after a battle - even if off map. 
	* Fix: Missing minor river at 2023 and 2123 for CME and CMF.
	* Fix: Heading alignment in currentHexView.
	* QA: accents missing on CME artifacts.
	* QA: More corrections for CMF terrain and traffic maps.
			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>1.18.3</title>
			<pubDate>1 Dec 2022</pubDate>
			<description>
				VERSION 1.18.3
				--------------
				* QA: Copyright and licence/license updates.
				* Fix: The minimal java version broke the update mechanism.
				* Enh: Four player CME (CMF) support.				
			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>1.18.1</title>
			<pubDate>6 Sep 2022</pubDate>
			<description>
				VERSION 1.18.1
				--------------
				* Fix: one version of a Challenger report in the Turn Report View.
				* Fix: Allow 'swap orders' to fix the bugged case when two orders appear as the same order twice.				
			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>1.18.0</title>
			<pubDate>11 Aug 2022</pubDate>
			<description>
				VERSION 1.18.0
				--------------
				To update to this version you MUST download the full installer for your operating system.	
				https://www.gamesystems.com/gamingsoftware/
				
				* Enh: This version includes a minimal version of java 11. No extra version of java is required.
			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>1.16.25</title>
			<pubDate>1 Aug 2022</pubDate>
			<description>
				VERSION 1.16.25
				---------------
    			* Fix: add Navy movement ranges
    			* Add: Fog of War for Fourth Ages games
    			* Fix: Orderchecker now correctly calculates movement for 850/860 orders and informs user when no movement style specified
    			* Fix: Corrected artifact second powers for 1650 and 2950 games
    			* Add: Added instructions for new users of JOverseer to empty map
    			* Fix: 840 Orders no longer cause freeze when auto-saved.
    			* Fix: Character name now displayed in 925 Recon pop-up
			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>1.16.24</title>
			<pubDate>24 June 2022</pubDate>
			<description>
				VERSION 1.16.24
				---------------
				* Fix: recent versions of java (>14) deprecated some required
				services, stopping jOverseer from starting, so a workaround was
				added.
			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>1.16.23</title>
			<pubDate>30 May 2022</pubDate>
			<description>
				VERSION 1.16.23
				---------------
				* Fix: Scry Area result wasn't parsed properly if the nation name was
				at the start of a line.
				* Fix: LAT order result parsing couldn't cope when the artifact was
				unnamed.
				* Fix: max chars allowed in nation statistics.
				* QA: Some rule violations in orderchecker, result in a dialog box
				which was particularly cryptic. For those cases, the character and
				order number have been added.
				* Enh:zoom 5 and 6 added for those of us with really big screens :)
			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>1.16.22</title>
			<pubDate>11 May 2021</pubDate>
			<description>
				VERSION 1.16.22
				---------------
				* Fix: CME rivers on the eastern edge.
				* Enh: Reflect recent game changes in the CME characters and
				artifacts.
			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>1.16.21</title>
			<pubDate>1 Mar 2021</pubDate>
			<description>
				VERSION 1.16.21
				---------------
				* Fix: The buy/sell bonus fix broke the market spend.
				* Fix: The nation borders for fog-of-war.
			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>1.16.20</title>
			<pubDate>1 Mar 2021</pubDate>
			<description>
				VERSION 1.16.20
				---------------
				* Fix: anti-virus was tagging joverseer.exe as a false positive.
			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>1.16.19</title>
			<pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021</pubDate>
			<description>
				VERSION 1.16.19
				---------------
				* Fix: Add batch file joverseer-no3D.bat to start JO without 3D
				acceleration for problematic NVidia graphics drivers on Windows.
				If you see overlapping JO frames etc, then use the file to replace the
				usual shortcut to start JO.
				* Fix: The order cost calculator now takes account of the buy/sell
				bonuses.
				* Fix: Timber and Mounts should now always be appearing in that
				order.
				* Fix: Warships and Transports should now always be appearing in that
				order.
			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>1.16.18</title>
			<pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020</pubDate>
			<description>
				VERSION 1.16.18
				---------------
				* Fix: Ordercheck order 948 now lets you transfer gold to a hidden PC
				* Fix: Orderchecker no longer gives a warning about casting Greater
				Heal.
				* Fix: Orderchecker will not choke on 175 orders.
				* Fix: From December 2020 the XML format changed. The tax base no
				longer includes sieged popcentres which fixes some discrepencies in
				reporting the economy.
				* Fix: The movement cost of a home move when moving evasively is now
				1.
				* Fix: Fourth Age games now notice reported popcentres on turn 0.
				Thanks Jeremy!
				* Enh: Game numbers greater than 999 are now supported.
				* Fix: The list of spells in the order editor are now sorted by
				number.
				* Enh: The recent games list now shows up to 10 recent games.
				* Fix: CME can now do the 942 order.
				* Enh: The Nation Statistics view now pulls in the number of NPCs
				recruited from the turn files.
				* Fix: The update web address is now https: the new version will try
				and correct http: if it finds them in preferences.
			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>1.16.17</title>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020</pubDate>
			<description>
				VERSION 1.16.17
				---------------
				* Enh: Orderchecker should now be checking for duplicate skills.
				* Enh: Orderchecker now spots missing orders.
				* Fix: various incorrect CME data.
				* Fix: Ticking the 'show climate' option on the Map Options View
				works again.
				You will only see changes if the selected turn was imported with this
				fixed version.
				* Fix: Camps really can't feed troops.
				* Fix: 585 is not a skill.
				* Fix: Don't restrict the spells a character can cast if they hold an
				artifact.
				* Fix: Order results weren't available if the character Id had
				trailing spaces.
				* Fix: Mage vs Mage challenges were confused over who won.
			</description>
		</item>

	</channel>
</rss>
