<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>Overseer releases</title>
		<link>https://www.middleearthgames.com/software/joverseer/feed.xml</link>
		<description>The latest version of jOverseer, the Middle-Earth game
			helper program.</description>
		<language>en</language>
		<item>
			<title>1.18.4</title>
			<pubDate>26 May 2023</pubDate>
			<description>
				VERSION 1.18.4
				--------------
	* Enh: Armies now appear to feed themselves from PCs in some cases.
	* Enh: Combat imports armies and PC. Added to hex pop-up menu.
		+ Thanks Jon!
	* Enh: Combat calc, add PC, estimate armies from recons.
	* Enh: Apply army size processing fix to all games, not just KS
	* Enh: default map zoom factor is saved as a preference.
	* Enh: Support randomized artifacts in 1650 games
		+ JO will re-write the known artifact ids to 0 when the first XML is imported.
	* Fix: Order-checking status should stay more in sync with the rest of JO.
	* Fix: Reveal Character True results now get recognised again in character reports.    
	* Fix: Orderchecker now notices two 810 orders.
	* Fix: Broken pdf parsing due to license name changes.
	* Fix: Marked JO as not dpiAware, and added some rendering hints to try and improve map hex readability.
	 (there are still problems with certain combinations)
	* Fix: Army maintenance calculation display in Army View.
	* Fix: Army composition display in Army View.
	* Fix: Captured/Lost PCs now recorded under new owner from battle report.
	* Fix: PC Size and Fort are now correct when reported in after a battle - even if off map. 
	* Fix: Missing minor river at 2023 and 2123 for CME and CMF.
	* Fix: Heading alignment in currentHexView.
	* QA: accents missing on CME artifacts.
	* QA: More corrections for CMF terrain and traffic maps.
			</description>
		</item>
		
		<item>
			<title>1.18.3</title>
			<pubDate>1 Dec 2022</pubDate>
			<description>
				VERSION 1.18.3
				--------------
				* QA: Copyright and licence/license updates.
				* Fix: The minimal java version broke the update mechanism.
				* Enh: Four player CME (CMF) support.				
			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>1.18.1</title>
			<pubDate>6 Sep 2022</pubDate>
			<description>
				VERSION 1.18.1
				--------------
				* Fix: one version of a Challenger report in the Turn Report View.
				* Fix: Allow 'swap orders' to fix the bugged case when two orders appear as the same order twice.				
			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>1.18.0</title>
			<pubDate>11 Aug 2022</pubDate>
			<description>
				VERSION 1.18.0
				--------------
				To update to this version you MUST download the full installer for your operating system.	
				https://www.middleearthgames.com/gamingsoftware/
				
				* Enh: This version includes a minimal version of java 11. No extra version of java is required.
			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>1.16.25</title>
			<pubDate>1 Aug 2022</pubDate>
			<description>
				VERSION 1.16.25
				---------------
    			* Fix: add Navy movement ranges
    			* Add: Fog of War for Fourth Ages games
    			* Fix: Orderchecker now correctly calculates movement for 850/860 orders and informs user when no movement style specified
    			* Fix: Corrected artifact second powers for 1650 and 2950 games
    			* Add: Added instructions for new users of JOverseer to empty map
    			* Fix: 840 Orders no longer cause freeze when auto-saved.
    			* Fix: Character name now displayed in 925 Recon pop-up
			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>1.16.24</title>
			<pubDate>24 June 2022</pubDate>
			<description>
				VERSION 1.16.24
				---------------
				* Fix: recent versions of java (>14) deprecated some required
				services, stopping jOverseer from starting, so a workaround was
				added.
			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>1.16.23</title>
			<pubDate>30 May 2022</pubDate>
			<description>
				VERSION 1.16.23
				---------------
				* Fix: Scry Area result wasn't parsed properly if the nation name was
				at the start of a line.
				* Fix: LAT order result parsing couldn't cope when the artifact was
				unnamed.
				* Fix: max chars allowed in nation statistics.
				* QA: Some rule violations in orderchecker, result in a dialog box
				which was particularly cryptic. For those cases, the character and
				order number have been added.
				* Enh:zoom 5 and 6 added for those of us with really big screens :)
			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>1.16.22</title>
			<pubDate>11 May 2021</pubDate>
			<description>
				VERSION 1.16.22
				---------------
				* Fix: CME rivers on the eastern edge.
				* Enh: Reflect recent game changes in the CME characters and
				artifacts.
			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>1.16.21</title>
			<pubDate>1 Mar 2021</pubDate>
			<description>
				VERSION 1.16.21
				---------------
				* Fix: The buy/sell bonus fix broke the market spend.
				* Fix: The nation borders for fog-of-war.
			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>1.16.20</title>
			<pubDate>1 Mar 2021</pubDate>
			<description>
				VERSION 1.16.20
				---------------
				* Fix: anti-virus was tagging joverseer.exe as a false positive.
			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>1.16.19</title>
			<pubDate>Mon, 22 Feb 2021</pubDate>
			<description>
				VERSION 1.16.19
				---------------
				* Fix: Add batch file joverseer-no3D.bat to start JO without 3D
				acceleration for problematic NVidia graphics drivers on Windows.
				If you see overlapping JO frames etc, then use the file to replace the
				usual shortcut to start JO.
				* Fix: The order cost calculator now takes account of the buy/sell
				bonuses.
				* Fix: Timber and Mounts should now always be appearing in that
				order.
				* Fix: Warships and Transports should now always be appearing in that
				order.
			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>1.16.18</title>
			<pubDate>Wed, 16 Dec 2020</pubDate>
			<description>
				VERSION 1.16.18
				---------------
				* Fix: Ordercheck order 948 now lets you transfer gold to a hidden PC
				* Fix: Orderchecker no longer gives a warning about casting Greater
				Heal.
				* Fix: Orderchecker will not choke on 175 orders.
				* Fix: From December 2020 the XML format changed. The tax base no
				longer includes sieged popcentres which fixes some discrepencies in
				reporting the economy.
				* Fix: The movement cost of a home move when moving evasively is now
				1.
				* Fix: Fourth Age games now notice reported popcentres on turn 0.
				Thanks Jeremy!
				* Enh: Game numbers greater than 999 are now supported.
				* Fix: The list of spells in the order editor are now sorted by
				number.
				* Enh: The recent games list now shows up to 10 recent games.
				* Fix: CME can now do the 942 order.
				* Enh: The Nation Statistics view now pulls in the number of NPCs
				recruited from the turn files.
				* Fix: The update web address is now https: the new version will try
				and correct http: if it finds them in preferences.
			</description>
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>1.16.17</title>
			<pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020</pubDate>
			<description>
				VERSION 1.16.17
				---------------
				* Enh: Orderchecker should now be checking for duplicate skills.
				* Enh: Orderchecker now spots missing orders.
				* Fix: various incorrect CME data.
				* Fix: Ticking the 'show climate' option on the Map Options View
				works again.
				You will only see changes if the selected turn was imported with this
				fixed version.
				* Fix: Camps really can't feed troops.
				* Fix: 585 is not a skill.
				* Fix: Don't restrict the spells a character can cast if they hold an
				artifact.
				* Fix: Order results weren't available if the character Id had
				trailing spaces.
				* Fix: Mage vs Mage challenges were confused over who won.
			</description>
		</item>

	</channel>
</rss>
