<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Overseer releases</title>
    <link>http://www.middleearthgames.com/software/joverseer/feed.xml</link>
    <description>The latest version of jOverseer, the Middle-Earth game helper program.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
    <title>1.0.12</title>
      <pubDate>Tue, 4 Mar 2014</pubDate>
      <description>
VERSION 1.0.12
--------------
	* Orderchecker
		o Enabled for Kinstrife.
		o Terrain maps and traffic maps corrected for Kinstrife.

		</description>
    </item>
    <item>
    <title>1.0.11</title>
      <pubDate>Mon, 3 Mar 2014</pubDate>
      <description>
VERSION 1.0.11
--------------

	* Updater
		o The Updater now spots windows and tries to run with elevated privileges if needed.
		o Added jOverseer.exe to launch jOverseer with the right java options and remove the dos window.
		o Running jOverseerUpdater.exe will always download the latest version.
		
	* Econo Calc
		o The economic calculator now correctly reports that "Your taxes will go up *by* n% to m%"
		
	* Current Hex View
		o Show Army movement is now a toggle. Click it again to remove the displayed range.
		o Show Character Movement Range is now a toggle.
		o The icon/button to display orders no longer jumps left/right when used.

	* Other
		o The Blue Wizard now appears in the Kinstrife characters.
		
		</description>
    </item>
    <item>
    <title>1.0.10</title>
      <pubDate>8 Jan 2014</pubDate>
      <description>
VERSION 1.0.10
--------------

    * Bug Fixes
    	o Symptom: no PC icon, Hex highlight unreliable, no order entry for hex.
    		+ There was a bug causing data corruption of Pop Centre.
    		+ Especially after a PC has been reduced to ruins.
    		+ There may be more than one cause. 
    		+ Please email a copy of the .jov file and a note of which hex shows the problem to middlearth.com.
    	o The Export Order Form no longer lets you mess around with the preformatted order.
    	o The movement calculator was getting confused when moving evasively.
    	 
		</description>
    </item>
        <item>
    <title>1.0.9</title>
      <pubDate>28 Nov 2014</pubDate>
      <description>
VERSION 1.0.9
-------------

	* The first release by MEPBM. 

	* Java JRE requirements are now 'Java 6' or better. Really you should be using 'Java version 7'. 
	
	* BOFA support
		o The BOFA games now use nations 1-5 instead of 10-14. This breaks compatibility with older BOFA games.

	* Visual tweaks
		o The descenders of order parameter text are no longer cut-off
		
	* XML errors
		o Error: null when reading some characters in new XML format
		o More helpful error when you read old format XML when expecting new format

		</description>
    </item>
    </channel>
</rss>