<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Overseer releases</title>
    <link>http://www.middleearthgames.com/software/joverseer/feed.xml</link>
    <description>The latest version of jOverseer, the Middle-Earth game helper program.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
    <title>1.16.9</title>
    <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018</pubDate>
    <description>
VERSION 1.16.9
--------------
	* Enh: The menus have been simplified. The Game menu is much simpler, and a new Advanced menu hides the less used stuff. 
	* Enh: You can save and exit from the 'are you sure you want to exit' dialog.
	* Enh: The Team Economy view has been updated to highlight tax rate increases, and tweaked to use totals consistent with the economy calculator.
	* Enh: The Team *Economies* view has been removed as it was confusing and duplicated information on the Team Economy view.
	* Enh: The various Nation filters (drop downs) will now hide dead nations, and those without economy information.
	* Enh: The Economy Calculator has been improved:
		o The totals have been overhauled and now should make obvious sense.
		o It remembers the selected nation when you change turn.
    	o It now works correctly for multiple orders of the same product in a nation.
    	o It shows the relevant SNAs
    * Enh: Merge Export Order Text and Export Order commands.
        o The two separate export orders were confusing.
        o The command automatically generates a 'nice' text representation of the order, which may be copied to the clipboard.
        o The Save and Submit buttons will use a different format of the orders that Middle-Earth Games and JOverseer understand.
        o The filename and time of the last submit is displayed.
	* Fix: The yellow warnings have been removed when casting spells for more than one artifact.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
    <title>1.16.8</title>
    <pubDate>Wed, 19 Sep 2018</pubDate>
    <description>
VERSION 1.16.8
--------------
	* Fix: People really wanted the order drop-down list back on the OrderEditorListView (despite it having problems not showing the character-restricted set of orders).
	* Fix: Some oddities with neutral armies not being show properly.
</description>
    </item>
    <item>
    <title>1.16.7</title>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2018</pubDate>
      <description>
VERSION 1.16.7
--------------
	* Fix: 1.16.6 broke order validation causing problems entering some orders.
	* Fix: CME rumors of NPC thieving caused a silent crash and data corruption on importing turn.
	</description>
	</item>
    <item>
    <title>1.16.6</title>
      <pubDate>Fri, 7 Sep 2018</pubDate>
      <description>
VERSION 1.16.6
--------------
    * Enh: Import Game Dir Tree, now imports in turn order instead of nation order (based on the filename).
    * Enh: Import Game Dir Tree, now defaults to the selected directory if it doesn't find any files in turn sub directories.
	* Enh: Import Text File now recognises that you've pasted the contents of an email file and selects the Automagic parser.
    * Enh: Add colours for the NPC nations 26 and 27.
    * Enh: Show population centres owned by NPC nations (CME).
	* Enh: The maximum number of characters allowed per nation is added to the Nation Stats View, and the Info View.
	* Fix: CME artifact numbers removed as they are randomised at game start.
	* Fix: Spot lore spell Locate Artifact results again.
	* Fix: Restore the filter order list view by meaningful stats (>29) rather than just >0.
	* Fix: The starting artifact names should display accents again.
	* Fix: If a character in JO had an artifact that wasn't recognised (separate bug), only the characters before that one were order checked.
	* Fix: The Order List View now again spots when the Order Editor changes an order.
    * Fix: Character ids with trailing spaces don't get mangled by the import process.
    * Fix: CME start data updated.
    * Fix: Add the abbreviations for CME nations.
    * Fix: Enable orderchecker for CME.
    * Fix: When the owner of a population centre wasn't recognised, it wasn't shown on the map.
    * Fix: Unable to show order results report when the character id was less than five characters long.
	* Fix: Orderchecker had the wrong data for NW hex features, which caused lots of confusion over movement costs.
	</description>
    </item>
	    <item>
    	<title>1.16.5</title>
      	<pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2018</pubDate>
      	<description>
VERSION 1.16.5
--------------
	* Fix: The order editor was ignoring *all* character skills in the order dropdown in new games.
	* Fix: Fourth Age game terrain was wrong for hex 0302.
		</description>
		</item>
	    <item>
    	<title>1.16.4</title>
      	<pubDate>Tue, 5 Jun 2018</pubDate>
      	<description>
VERSION 1.16.4
--------------
	* Enh: Support for the new Champions of Middle Earth module, although order checking is currently missing.
	* Enh: If you are using an obsolete version of java, you will get a warning at update time.
	* Fix: Orderchecker is working again for those who found it broken in 1.16.3.
	* Fix: Orderchecker data files now live in the orderchecker.jar file by default. Bare files in the filesystem will override them.
	* Fix: Those running older versions of java which broke on joverseer 1.16.3. 
	* Fix: The characterset used for the data files is treated as UTF-8 and several names now have the correct accents.
	* FIx: lots of uses of Hex locations omitted the leading 0.
	* Fix: Sorting by Popcentre level and fortifications.
</description>
</item>
	    <item>
    	<title>1.16.3</title>
      	<pubDate>Wed, 18 Apr 2018</pubDate>
      	<description>
VERSION 1.16.3
--------------
	* Enh: Menu Help now has item Check For Update which forces the check to happen on request, rather than once every two weeks.
	* Enh: additional command to restore layout to a simpler, automagic style layout.
	* Fix: issue #627 now checks for SNA 22 when building the list of possible orders in the order editor
	* Fix: Popcentres should have their accents back.
	* Fix: Some odd accents in artifacts and spells.
	* Fix: pdf imports no longer report benign null errors.
	* Fix: issue #653 order view filter - characters with/without orders - now understands characters with more than 3 orders
	* Fix: In the Map Option View, If you changed to allegiance colours, then you couldn't get back to nation colours
	* Fix: default nation names for FA
	* Fix: orderchecker and 940 412 order  
	</description>
    </item>

    <item>
    	<title>1.16.2</title>
      	<pubDate>Tue, 1 Aug 2017</pubDate>
      	<description>
VERSION 1.16.2
--------------
	* Enh: Cast Lore Spell 412 now supports up to 6 parameters.
	* Fix: 120 Order wasn't being helpful in order editor.
	* Fix/Enhancement: UTF-8 encoding handled in metadata files. If an external editor put a Byte Order Mark in a metadata file, then JO could miss-read the first line. e.g. the 120 bug.
	* Enh: Create Army and Character now added to current hex view popup menu.
	* Fix: KS army missing from 3222. 
	* Fix: FA roads and rivers updated.
	* Fix: Merged fix to metadata paths from alexey-mr and extended. It should help non-Windows users.
	* Fix: Open Software licence is now explicitly BSD.
      	</description>
    </item>
    <item>
    	<title>1.16.1</title>
      	<pubDate>Wed, 7 Jun 2017</pubDate>
      	<description>
VERSION 1.16.1
--------------
	* Fix: you can now create new 1000 games.
	</description>
    </item>
    <item>
		<title>1.16.0</title>
      	<pubDate>Wed, 7 Jun 2017</pubDate>
      	<description>
VERSION 1.16.0
--------------
	* Clarified some the column names in the Economy Team View.
    * New filters in Order List View.
	* The same as the 1.15.5 beta version.
	* Fix for automatic updating on macs
	* Fix: 935 recon result is now recognised.
	* Fix: 910 scouting result is now recognised.
    * Fix for macs.
    * Fixed crash in 2950 new game.
	* starting information for 2950 games has been significantly corrected.
	* 990 order (one ring) shouldn't be flagged yellow in orderchecker
	* Fixed: java8 selects IPv6 for networking which breaks email sending.
	* automatic recognition of new XML format so no need for user to pick.
	* right arrow symbol now correctly displayed.
	* Fix 622: Kinstrife roads selected at game setup no longer vanish.
	* Fix 632: Player characters with less than 5 characters in their name, had odd things happening, eg no past orders etc. Rebuilding the .jov file is needed to actually see a difference.
	* Artifact effect descriptions are now consistent for saner sorting.
      	</description>
    </item>
    </channel>
</rss>