<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>Overseer Test (development) releases</title>
		<link>http://www.gamesystems.com/software/joverseer/testfeed.xml</link>
		<description>The latest version of jOverseer, the Middle-Earth game
			helper program.</description>
		<language>en</language>
		<item>
			<title>1.16.6</title>
			<pubDate>Fri, 27 August 2018</pubDate>
			<description>
				VERSION 1.16.6
				--------------
				* Enh: Import Game Dir Tree, now imports in turn order instead of
				nation order (based on the filename).
				* Enh: Import Game Dir Tree, now defaults to the selected directory
				if it doesn't find any files in turn sub directories.
				* Enh: Import Text File now recognises that you've pasted the
				contents of an email file and selects the Automagic parser.
				* Enh: Add colours for the NPC nations 26 and 27.
				* Enh: Show population centres owned by NPC nations (CME).
				* Enh: The maximum number of characters allowed per nation is added
				to the Nation Stats View, and the Info View.
				* Fix: CME artifact numbers removed as they are randomised at game
				start.
				* Fix: Spot lore spell Locate Artifact results again.
				* Fix: Restore the filter order list view by meaningful stats (>29)
				rather than just >0.
				* Fix: The starting artifact names should display accents again.
				* Fix: If a character in JO had an artifact that wasn't recognised
				(separate bug), only the characters before that one were order
				checked.
				* Fix: The Order List View now again spots when the Order Editor
				changes an order.
				* Fix: Character ids with trailing spaces don't get mangled by the
				import process.
				* Fix: CME start data updated (again).
				* Fix: Add the abbreviations for CME nations.
				* Fix: Enable orderchecker for CME.
				* Fix: When the owner of a population centre wasn't recognised, it
				wasn't shown on the map.
				* Fix: Unable to show order results report when the character id was
				less than five characters long.
				* Fix: Orderchecker had the wrong data for NW hex features, which
				caused lots of confusion over movement costs.
			</description>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>