<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<rss version="2.0">
  <channel>
    <title>Overseer Beta (development) releases</title>
    <link>http://www.middleearthgames.com/software/joverseer/betafeed.xml</link>
    <description>The latest version of jOverseer, the Middle-Earth game helper program.</description>
    <language>en</language>
    <item>
    <title>1.15.9</title>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Apr 2017</pubDate>
      <description>
VERSION 1.15.5
--------------
	test version for mac update testing.
VERSION 1.15.4
--------------
	* Fix: 935 recon result is now recognised.
	* Fix: 910 scouting result is now recognised.     
VERSION 1.15.3
--------------
    * Fix for macs.
VERSION 1.15.2
--------------
    * Fixed crash in 2950 new game.
VERSION 1.15.1
--------------
	* starting information for 2950 games has been significantly corrected.
	* 990 order (one ring) shouldn't be flagged yellow in orderchecker
	* Fixed: java8 selects IPv6 for networking which breaks email sending.
	* automatic recognition of new XML format so no need for user to pick.
	* right arrow symbol now correctly displayed.
	* Fix 622: Kinstrife roads selected at game setup no longer vanish.
	* Fix 632: Player characters with less than 5 characters in their name, had odd things happening, eg no past orders etc. Rebuilding the .jov file is needed to actually see a difference.
	* Artifact effect descriptions are now consistent for saner sorting.
	
VERSION 1.13.9-11
--------------
    * version bump to test distribution.
VERSION 1.13.8
--------------
	* layout files moved to user directory. JOverseer directory can now live as readonly in Program Files in windows.          
VERSION 1.13.7
--------------
  	* Ant based and Eclipse compatible build and release system rewritten.
	* Windows installer updated for new installs.
	* log files now written to temp directory instead of console.
	
VERSION 1.13.6
--------------
    * Validation of switching from version control hosting from subversion on googlecode to git on GitHub.
	
VERSION 1.13.5
--------------
	* Internationalization
		o preliminary italian support added.
		o better spanish coverage.
		
VERSION 1.13.4
--------------
	* Version numbering change.
		o This version is 1.13.0 rather than 1.0.13.
		o This is a developer or 'beta' version, as will be all versions where the middle part is an odd number.
		o The next stable release will be based on this one (probably) but called 1.14.0.
		o All future stable releases will have even middle parts to the version number.
		o The final version part number will increase with minor versions.
		o Once you have a stable version of jOverseer installed, the auto-update mechanism will not switch you from a stable to beta version.
		 
	* Platform support
		o Recent versions of java (version 7 update 9 and later) have changed some of the look and feel support, which broke jOverseer.
		o This most obviously affected Macs, but also others.
		o This is fixed for some users, further solutions are being considered.
		
	* Current Hex View
		o Bug Fix: An empty list of characters being shown using the new default mergesort in java 7+. 
		
	* Internationalization
		o Widespread changes to improve support for different countries and languages (locales).
		o The messages.properties file now should have all the translatable text.
		o The only sample (incomplete) version available is messages_es.properties for Spanish readers.
		o Orderchecker is not included, and the orders themselves are still in English.
		o For the curious and if you want to force the selection of a locale, there is a command line option. For example '-L es' will select spanish.
		
	* Orderchecker
		o Fixed so that characters only seen on PDF reports don't stop orderchecker running.
		o Fixed so that it uses the current turn terrain and traffic map and allegiances instead of it's predefined ones.
		o Fixed so that you can issue a challenge when travelling with an army.
		o Fixed so that it spots a buy food order before a move, so army is 'fed'

	* Edit Nation Allegiance
		o Fixed a bug which resulted in a change in allegiance being partially propagated to future turns. This caused Orderchecker to get confused about changed allegiances especially for Tirkhor and Khazad in Kinstrife games.

		</description>
    </item>
    </channel>
</rss>